module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What is the capital city of Canada?', 
    a: 'Montreal',
    b: 'Ottawa',
    c: 'Vancouver',
    d: 'Quebec City',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: '"Lap Band" surgery is used to treat which condition?', 
    a: 'Obesity',
    b: 'Infertility',
    c: 'Back Pain',
    d: 'Hyperthyroidism',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Adolphus Busch was best known for starting what kind of company?', 
    a: 'Oil',
    b: 'Bank',
    c: 'Sausage',
    d: 'Beer',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'In the popcorn industry, what term is used to refer to kernels that don\'t pop?', 
    a: 'Old Maids',
    b: 'Busts',
    c: 'Geese',
    d: 'Bombs',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the first name of former U.S. president Garfield?', 
    a: 'Benjamin',
    b: 'John',
    c: 'Andrew',
    d: 'James',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following snakes is poisonous?', 
    a: 'Garter',
    b: 'Rat',
    c: 'Boa',
    d: 'Cobra',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Sherwood Forest is associated with what legend?', 
    a: 'King Arthur',
    b: 'Robin Hood',
    c: 'The Hobbit',
    d: 'Lord of the Rings',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Warren Buffett is the CEO of what company?', 
    a: 'Fannie Mae',
    b: 'Walmart',
    c: 'Berkshire Hathaway',
    d: 'General Electric',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the fear of dreams called?', 
    a: 'Oneirophobia',
    b: 'Agoraphobia',
    c: 'Hemophobia',
    d: 'Acrophobia',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which sport was reintroduced into the Olympic games in 2016?', 
    a: 'Golf',
    b: 'Water Polo',
    c: 'Badminton',
    d: 'Archery',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];
